I'm beginning to think that this is a
bot thing.
Why are you so obsessed about this?
Like, okay, she lied.
I could see if she lied and like harmed
people,
but she was on my podcast and she was
brilliant.
I think it's [ __ ] up that she lies.
>> So, to address the first question, which
was do I believe that I have some
narcissistic traits in my
low-functioning behavior? Absolutely.
For me to be able to emasculate that
man, and he's just loving on me, he's
never disempowered me. This man wasn't
cheating or beating on me. He was there
all day.
>> Do you struggle with the same things
that I struggle with? Self-importance.
>> Mm, not at this level. Do I have a high
level of self-love and high and and and
self-value? Yes. Can my confidence be on
steroids? Sometimes, because that's the
way I inspire me. Yeah. Does my
self-talk show up externally? Sometimes,
yeah. Is my self-talk narcissistic?
Absa-fucking-lutely.
>> on things that they don't know about.
And my autism diagnosis is not for you
all to discuss.
It's not up for your debate. And anyone
who is speaking on or trying to
invalidate diagnosis that comes outside
of a clinician is only repeat revealing
that they actually don't know anything
about autism diagnosis or autism.
So I just want to once again thank you
all about autism diagnosis only repeat
revealing that they actually don't know
anything or trying to invalidate
diagnosis that comes outside of a
clinician is only repeat revealing that
they actually don't know anything about
autism diagnosis or autism.
So
>> you want to blame something on somebody,
you're going to blame them
blame that they're narcissists.
But again, as I was saying earlier, a
lot of people that's autistic and it's
very difficult to tease out whether
somebody is borderline at times, whether
somebody is autistic at times, or
whether somebody is narcissistic
or antisocial
or what have you. You know what I'm
saying? Because they kind of all look
alike if you're not a trained clinician
from a clinician. And what I'm arguing
is
that it is very difficult for trained
clinicians to come up with that
diagnosis.
>> Right.
>> what I mean? So
but the confidence that she speaks with
and actually it's not surprising to me
now when you think about what she said
in that clip.
It's not surprising.
It's not surprising that she said what
she said. Well, we're going to play
uh uh
pretty soon here
because the fact is that she doesn't
seem to really
respect
in many ways
the science
of mental health.
This is where we're going to get to.
Like this is the one of the clips I want
to show you where I say that Amanda
Seales is out of pocket.
Amanda Seales is
showing a bit that she's a bit of a What
do they call it? Hypocrite.
And maybe not even a hypocrite cuz she
does not perhaps believe that mental
health is serious
for whatever reason, but she wants you
to do this. She wants you to respect
her.
>> And you know, for all purposes, and I
just want to also just bring this to
light for you because this is going to
be a theme throughout this interview.
>> Okay.
>> I am a scholar of race.
>> I'm not just someone who experiences it.
I'm a scholar. I'm an academic of race.
So, I see the world through a particular
lens because I am skilled at doing so
and because I'm an expert at doing so.
Like my master's isn't just in
African-American studies. It's the fact
that I was taught by some of the
greatest thought leaders of our time.
>> Mhm.
>> So, when you hear me say these things, I
would just like to ask that
because you have someone who is an
expert sitting in front of you to just
consider versus be combative because
there may be an opportunity here to see
something differently because you have
someone with you who is not just
experiencing race, but is also
uh examining and there's a different
there's a different intellectualism
about that. You know what I mean?
>> Yeah.
>> Different intellectualism about that.
And I and I say that also because that's
why I went and got my master's. I went
and got my master's because I know that
we live in a world that loves to try and
find ways to undermine black people's
minds. They love to find ways to
undermine black people's intellect. Look
at this
>> I just don't care.
>> And I think one of the reasons why a lot
of individuals will say it's not that
deep or state that it's just
entertainment is because one, you think
mental health and psychology is just
folk wisdom and it's not. It's a
science. And two, you guys are very
insulated from the field that you claim
to be discussing because you don't work
in that field and you haven't in quite
some time. But as someone who walks into
the offices and sees the clients and
goes to the talks and does the community
programs, we are struggling.
And every and these little entertainment
only pieces that are spreading
misinformation, you're doing more harm
for the black community than you know.
And the reason why you don't know is cuz
you're so insulated from the black
community. You just sit in front of
these mics and you make all these money
and you do all these patrons and you
wear these crazy hats and you do all
that. But I would actually say I I don't
see these kind of places as pro-black.
I don't.
And the only way you would know that is
if you did the work that I do. And
you're never going to because one,
you're not qualified.
And two, it would break you down.
>> I'm beginning to think that this is a
bot thing.
Why are you so obsessed about this?
Like, okay, she lied.
I could see if she lied and like harms
people,
but she was on my podcast and she was
brilliant.
I think it's [ __ ] up that she lied.
You know, and then that's that. The the
the need to
If y'all went this hard against like
Kamala Harris for supporting a genocide,
then like what would That that would
matter to me.
I don't I don't have There's no match. I
don't need to have some type of debate
with Dr. Cheyenne with Cheyenne Bryant.
At the end of the day, for some reason,
she felt like she needed to lie about
credentials.
I don't know why.
I think part of the reason is because we
live in a a world where we act like
credentials is what determines
somebody's effectiveness across the
board. And in some respects, it
absolutely necessary. And in her
respect, it actually wasn't necessary
for her to do the work that she does.
That being said, I just don't care.
I don't care.
She was on my podcast and she was
incredible. I don't care.
I think it sucks and I think it was not
and I think that at the end of the day,
there are people who work really hard to
get doctorates. There are also people
who call themselves doctor when they get
an honorary doctorate, and I don't think
that's much different.
I don't think it's much different.
Maya Angelou was walking around calling
herself Dr. Maya Angelou. She didn't
complete a doctorate.
>> So, again, I I I I just think that, you
know, um her au- that autism doesn't
Autism doesn't equate to, pardon my
language, [ __ ]
And I'm just being real honest. It
doesn't. And I see a lot of similarity
between her and Cheyenne.
I see a lot of similarity between her
and Omar.
I see a lot of similarity, you know,
like this sister literally goes on
Shannon and say Shannon's Sharper Show
and says,
you know,
says this.
>> This is going to be a theme throughout
this interview.
>> Okay.
>> I am a scholar of race.
>> I'm not just someone who experiences it.
I'm a scholar. I'm an academic of race.
So, I see the world through a particular
lens because I am skilled at doing so,
and because I'm an expert at doing so.
Like, my master's isn't just in
African-American studies. It's the fact
that I was taught by some of the
greatest thought leaders of our time.
So, when
>> So,
this is what she says, right?
>> Mhm.
>> So, she wants her degree
as a scholar of race. Now, anybody look
me up.
Look me up.
Look up my dissertation.
I don't know what her diss- I forgot
what she said her dissertation was on,
but it was like hip hop or something
like that.
>> Yeah.
>> And then when she says race, she's
talking about just blackness, so African
or whatever. Maybe she's talking about
that.
Um but the reality I think they were
talking about racism or something like
that if I remember that interview, what
have you. I can't recall.
I mean, hold up. They were talking about
the little child, too. I mean, I I think
I Hold up. Shannon was saying like with
the little child Yeah, yeah, it was
about racism.
And Shannon was pushing back. Well,
Shannon was doing some stuff that, you
know, that she was checking him on. Let
me just be keep that 100.
But,
the reality is that doesn't mean that
his question wasn't relevant. And maybe
And it doesn't mean that you couldn't
educate him on it.
You know what I mean? Just the fact that
you can't even be questioned. That's
That's That's very That That That sounds
like very treaty. Let me just say
treaty.
That seems very treaty.
Typically, what you see with people with
with autism is that they they literally
don't get caught all up in that type of
thing. They just tell you the facts
again.
She didn't give no facts. She just said,
"Believe me."
Like that that that wasn't like like
from from
A lot of autistic people, they're like,
"Hold up. That might make sense." IF YOU
CAN LITERALLY
IF YOU LITERALLY CAN MAKE SOME SENSE for
a lot of people on the spectrum, they
they can think about it again. I'm just
being real honest. Like people are like
neurodivergent who see things in these
very literal and black and white and,
you know, type of ways and kind of like,
"No, they If you make sense,
you can change like it might not be
about the feelings all the time.
It might be more about Hold That's a
literal fact, Shannon.
And Shannon did state a literal fact.
And sometimes that is what the coldness
comes out. It's not that you're a
[ __ ] Excuse my language.
But, see, that's what I'm saying. So,
her being an A-hole
is different than what we see on
the spectrum, perhaps. See, people on
the spectrum often are seen as A-holes
because they're just telling you the
truth.
That's different. That's very different.
No, she's She's gaslighting Is she's
credentialing here.
She's telling you, look, hold up little
boy. Let me show you how great I am with
my degree. I am a scholar, but she ain't
tell you the facts. She just told you
why you supposed to listen to her. She
told YOU WHY YOU SUPPOSED to listen to
her. She didn't give you any data. She
didn't support She did not articulate
why
as a scholar. She just told you she is a
scholar. There's a brother here in
Baltimore who been taking shot pop shots
at me. He probably pop shots at me. He
might be listening to this cuz he does.
And all he can tell you about is how
great he is. He been taking pop shots at
me with his honorary doctorate. Talking
about, oh, these people with real
doctorate doctorate. Like he been taking
Like I can't see him. So, when I call
him out,
you know, he he get a little ruffled.
But the reality is this, he doesn't tell
you anything. He just tell you how many
books he read. I read 2,000 books a
year, 100 books a year over the last 20
years, so you supposed to listen to me.
I said, well, tell me what you read
first.
I don't know what It's not about what
you
It's not about what you read or what
degree you got. SHOW ME THAT YOU GOT THE
god damn thing.
Let me hear your analysis.
I'M NOT THAT PEOPLE A LOT OF us get
really caught up into the idea that
a person read books. See, cuz these
people know with these personality
traits that people
are in awe with the fact that you said
you read so many books. And they
literally believe you. They know that we
we believe some foolishness at times.
Katt Williams said he read how many
books?
See,
the industry is full of them.
Some of your greatest thespians,
Terrence Howard. I DON'T KNOW HOW MANY
PEOPLE
I had to tell them that Terrence Howard
is all out his god damn on mind.
But see we we we're very gullible and we
and and see because we've been hurt by
this society,
as a scholar of racism myself and
trauma, because we've been hurt so bad
by this society,
we will look for anything
that like like like we're counter
everything to a degree.
And this is how
people
like these folks
abuse their information. Like Cat
Williams know he didn't read all them
god damn on books.
And most people who aren't traumatized
by this racist society know he ain't
read them god damn on books.
I know y'all going to say, "Well,
everybody's traumatized." See, no, we
can't just do that.
We at least got to put some level of a
measure on it to say, "Well, we're
traumatized differently if we're all
traumatized." We all do have um
we all do have pain and hurt and
everything does not
qualify or quantify at the level of
being traumatized. See, but again, you
have to talk to an expert about that.
But again, she's talking about she's an
expert.
Let me get to my notes real quick what I
just wrote down as I was listening to
it.
She said she has a master's degree.
She says that
from the greatest thought leaders
in the in the in the world have have
have taught her.
See again, not all people with these
traits literally show up
and don't have a degree.
A lot of them go to these institutions
to validate them.
See again, that doesn't mean that like
like for example, people keep talking
about Umar really has a degree. HE DOES.
BUT IT DOESN'T MEAN HE COULD HAVE ALL
SIX OF THEM. BUT, WHAT was the driving
factor for him to get those degrees?
See, these people
with these type of personalities seek
out anything to validate them. Some
people do the hard route, and some
people make it up like Cheyenne.
I'm assuming she made some of it up. And
they all tend to find these Christian
heritage type of institutions, and they
get these honorary doctorates and all
and and this craziness is that they
never get enough for a lot of them. So,
that's different. They're on a spectrum,
too. Some of them are smarter than
others.
That guy, Richie. I'm sorry, y'all. I'm
still listening to him.
I'm not saying he doesn't put out some
some halfway decent information, but the
brother got 15 degrees, bro.
He got 15 or what is it? 15, 16 degrees
now. Like, okay. Like, it like who in
their mind he's a JD?
He's a uh he's a some type of uh
neurological sciences or something. I
don't know. He
I I might be getting him wrong. He's a
he's a he's going to medical school now.
He's uh
This brother said he got
15, 16 degrees. See, that's when your
your level of grandiosity has no limit.
Where you where where where you become
so smart that you dumb. It's like
polite.
It's like
it's this this these traits that they
speak about as she spoke about.
They have you more confident.
So confident that you're dumb.
You you're so confident when you got
these traits that people call
narcissistic.
You're so confident that you don't you
don't think that you'll get caught. You
think that you will
beat the system.
Again,
she's not trying to destroy the system.
She's not trying to She's trying to
abuse the system. I'm talking about
Cheyenne.
She's trying to abuse the system.
So, again,
um oh, let me let me close out with
these notes real quick. Um
She says
she's an expert on race.
She She speaks about why did why does
people care about
Cheyenne,
this one person.
Cheyenne is just
one example of many of these people that
we need to call out.
She's one example
and she will cause harm. She will She
will cause harm.
She even said it herself that she has
due to her narcissistic traits.
Umar will and has caused harm. But, I
got brothers on my page. You know, they
can't do the thing.
>> So, let let us be.
>> the work that she does. That being said,
I just don't care.
>> And I think one of the reasons why a lot
of individuals will say it's not that
deep or state that it's just
entertainment is because one, you think
mental health and psychology is just
folk wisdom and it's not, it's a
science. And two, you guys are very
insulated from the field that you claim
to be discussing because you don't work
in that field and you haven't in quite
some time. But, as someone who walks
into the offices and sees the clients
and goes to the talks and does the
community programs, we are struggling.
And every And these little entertainment
only pieces that are spreading
misinformation, you're doing more harm
for the black community than you know.
And the reason why you don't know is cuz
you're so insulated from the black
community. You just sit in front of
these mics and you make all these money
and you do all these Patreons and you
wear these crazy hats and you do all
that. But, I would actually say I I
don't see these kind of places as
pro-black.
I don't.
And the only way you would know that is
if you did the work that I do. And
you're never going to because one,
you're not qualified.
And two, it would break you down.
>> I don't care.
>> And family, with that
I think that's a great closing. And I
agree. Be careful
where you get your information at.
Even those who are calling her calling
her out, Cheyenne,
especially
on these platforms getting clicks and
views, those who tell the story the
best,
they are full of misinformation.
Make sure you talk to some real trained
clinicians cuz the nuance is so complex.
These people are saying all types of bad
information out there, Miles. I'm saying
everything from the institution to uh
all the complexities that is very
difficult for people in the field to
even know. I'm a counselor educator.
I've been trained in educate in
educating people about these things.
And this is just a tip of the iceberg.
It's a complex field that most of us
don't really know any a lot of us don't
know anything about. In fact, before
yesterday before this happened, most of
us didn't know that psychologist wasn't
the only people practicing
psychotherapy.
And then you and psychologist, you have
to have a doc doctorate degree and and
take licensing at that level.
But again, family,
we're going to say thanks for joining
us. Like, share, subscribe. Hype, hype.
You know what I mean?
Uh make sure you get good information.
Send the people over here. Send the
people over to these other licensed
clinical professionals.
Or you know, just people with same
minds.
Uh that's kind of hard to figure out,
but you know what I mean.
Vet everybody, including me. Peace and
power.
>> When you claim you have finished, you're
going to get your MIND BACK. WHEN YOU
CLAIM YOUR AFRICAN IS YOU'RE GOING TO
GET YOUR MIND BACK. When you claim your
African is you're going to get your mind
back.
When you claim your African is you're
going to get your mind back.